export const chapter6StudyData = [
  // Key Terms
  {
    id: "KT601",
    front: "acquisition",
    back: "period of initial learning in classical conditioning in which a human or an animal begins to connect a neutral stimulus and an unconditioned stimulus so that the neutral stimulus will begin to elicit the conditioned response"
  },
  {
    id: "KT602",
    front: "associative learning",
    back: "form of learning that involves connecting certain stimuli or events that occur together in the environment (classical and operant conditioning)"
  },
  {
    id: "KT603",
    front: "classical conditioning",
    back: "learning in which the stimulus or experience occurs before the behavior and then gets paired or associated with the behavior"
  },
  {
    id: "KT604",
    front: "cognitive map",
    back: "mental picture of the layout of the environment"
  },
  {
    id: "KT605",
    front: "conditioned response (CR)",
    back: "response caused by the conditioned stimulus"
  },
  {
    id: "KT606",
    front: "conditioned stimulus (CS)",
    back: "stimulus that elicits a response due to its being paired with an unconditioned stimulus"
  },
  {
    id: "KT607",
    front: "continuous reinforcement",
    back: "rewarding a behavior every time it occurs"
  },
  {
    id: "KT608",
    front: "extinction",
    back: "decrease in the conditioned response when the unconditioned stimulus is no longer paired with the conditioned stimulus"
  },
  {
    id: "KT609",
    front: "fixed interval reinforcement schedule",
    back: "behavior is rewarded after a set amount of time"
  },
  {
    id: "KT610",
    front: "fixed ratio reinforcement schedule",
    back: "set number of responses must occur before a behavior is rewarded"
  },
  {
    id: "KT611",
    front: "habituation",
    back: "when we learn not to respond to a stimulus that is presented repeatedly without change"
  },
  {
    id: "KT612",
    front: "higher-order conditioning (also, second-order conditioning)",
    back: "using a conditioned stimulus to condition a neutral stimulus"
  },
  {
    id: "KT613",
    front: "instinct",
    back: "unlearned knowledge, involving complex patterns of behavior; instincts are thought to be more prevalent in lower animals than in humans"
  },
  {
    id: "KT614",
    front: "latent learning",
    back: "learning that occurs, but it may not be evident until there is a reason to demonstrate it"
  },
  {
    id: "KT615",
    front: "law of effect",
    back: "behavior that is followed by consequences satisfying to the organism will be repeated and behaviors that are followed by unpleasant consequences will be discouraged"
  },
  {
    id: "KT616",
    front: "learning",
    back: "change in behavior or knowledge that is the result of experience"
  },
  {
    id: "KT617",
    front: "model",
    back: "person who performs a behavior that serves as an example (in observational learning)"
  },
  {
    id: "KT618",
    front: "negative punishment",
    back: "taking away a pleasant stimulus to decrease or stop a behavior"
  },
  {
    id: "KT619",
    front: "negative reinforcement",
    back: "taking away an undesirable stimulus to increase a behavior"
  },
  {
    id: "KT620",
    front: "neutral stimulus (NS)",
    back: "stimulus that does not initially elicit a response"
  },
  {
    id: "KT621",
    front: "observational learning",
    back: "type of learning that occurs by watching others"
  },
  {
    id: "KT622",
    front: "operant conditioning",
    back: "form of learning in which the stimulus/experience happens after the behavior is demonstrated"
  },
  {
    id: "KT623",
    front: "partial reinforcement",
    back: "rewarding behavior only some of the time"
  },
  {
    id: "KT624",
    front: "positive punishment",
    back: "adding an undesirable stimulus to stop or decrease a behavior"
  },
  {
    id: "KT625",
    front: "positive reinforcement",
    back: "adding a desirable stimulus to increase a behavior"
  },
  {
    id: "KT626",
    front: "primary reinforcer",
    back: "has innate reinforcing qualities (e.g., food, water, shelter, sex)"
  },
  {
    id: "KT627",
    front: "punishment",
    back: "implementation of a consequence in order to decrease a behavior"
  },
  {
    id: "KT628",
    front: "reflex",
    back: "unlearned, automatic response by an organism to a stimulus in the environment"
  },
  {
    id: "KT629",
    front: "reinforcement",
    back: "implementation of a consequence in order to increase a behavior"
  },
  {
    id: "KT630",
    front: "secondary reinforcer",
    back: "has no inherent value unto itself and only has reinforcing qualities when linked with something else (e.g., money, gold stars, poker chips)"
  },
  {
    id: "KT631",
    front: "shaping",
    back: "rewarding successive approximations toward a target behavior"
  },
  {
    id: "KT632",
    front: "spontaneous recovery",
    back: "return of a previously extinguished conditioned response"
  },
  {
    id: "KT633",
    front: "stimulus discrimination",
    back: "ability to respond differently to similar stimuli"
  },
  {
    id: "KT634",
    front: "stimulus generalization",
    back: "demonstrating the conditioned response to stimuli that are similar to the conditioned stimulus"
  },
  {
    id: "KT635",
    front: "unconditioned response (UCR)",
    back: "natural (unlearned) behavior to a given stimulus"
  },
  {
    id: "KT636",
    front: "unconditioned stimulus (UCS)",
    back: "stimulus that elicits a reflexive response"
  },
  {
    id: "KT637",
    front: "variable interval reinforcement schedule",
    back: "behavior is rewarded after unpredictable amounts of time have passed"
  },
  {
    id: "KT638",
    front: "variable ratio reinforcement schedule",
    back: "number of responses differ before a behavior is rewarded"
  },
  {
    id: "KT639",
    front: "vicarious punishment",
    back: "process where the observer sees the model punished, making the observer less likely to imitate the model's behavior"
  },
  {
    id: "KT640",
    front: "vicarious reinforcement",
    back: "process where the observer sees the model rewarded, making the observer more likely to imitate the model's behavior"
  },
  // Review Questions
  {
    id: "R601",
    front: "Which of the following is an example of a reflex that occurs at some point in the development of a human being?",
    back: "infant sucking on a nipple"
  },
  {
    id: "R602",
    front: "Learning is best defined as a relatively permanent change in behavior that ________.",
    back: "occurs as a result of experience"
  },
  {
    id: "R603",
    front: "Two forms of associative learning are ________ and ________.",
    back: "classical conditioning; operant conditioning"
  },
  {
    id: "R604",
    front: "In ________ the stimulus or experience occurs before the behavior and then gets paired with the behavior.",
    back: "classical conditioning"
  },
  {
    id: "R605",
    front: "A stimulus that does not initially elicit a response in an organism is a(n) ________.",
    back: "neutral stimulus"
  },
  {
    id: "R606",
    front: "In Watson and Rayner's experiments, Little Albert was conditioned to fear a white rat, and then he began to be afraid of other furry white objects. This demonstrates ________.",
    back: "stimulus generalization"
  },
  {
    id: "R607",
    front: "Extinction occurs when ________.",
    back: "the conditioned stimulus is presented repeatedly without being paired with an unconditioned stimulus"
  },
  {
    id: "R608",
    front: "In Pavlov's work with dogs, the psychic secretions were ________.",
    back: "conditioned responses"
  },
  {
    id: "R609",
    front: "________ is when you take away a pleasant stimulus to stop a behavior.",
    back: "negative punishment"
  },
  {
    id: "R610",
    front: "Which of the following is not an example of a primary reinforcer?",
    back: "money"
  },
  {
    id: "R611",
    front: "Rewarding successive approximations toward a target behavior is ________.",
    back: "shaping"
  },
  {
    id: "R612",
    front: "Slot machines reward gamblers with money according to which reinforcement schedule?",
    back: "variable ratio"
  },
  {
    id: "R613",
    front: "The person who performs a behavior that serves as an example is called a ________.",
    back: "model"
  },
  {
    id: "R614",
    front: "In Bandura's Bobo doll study, when the children who watched the aggressive model were placed in a room with the doll and other toys, they ________.",
    back: "kicked and threw the doll"
  },
  {
    id: "R615",
    front: "Which is the correct order of steps in the modeling process?",
    back: "attention, retention, reproduction, motivation"
  },
  {
    id: "R616",
    front: "Who proposed observational learning?",
    back: "Albert Bandura"
  }
];